{
    "id": "d8ce2fc57c3a440e9c89e8126efe9bb2",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The Minister has …………………… to come.",
            "description": "Before an infinitive, we use agree, not accept.",
            "answers": [
                "accepted",
                "agreed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "In most countries you have to be …………………….. 18 to drive a car.",
            "description": "We use over to talk about ages and speeds. ",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys swam ……………………….. the river.",
            "description": "We usually prefer across to talk about movement in water.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "along",
                "over",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. scientists, smoking can cause cancer.",
            "description": "According to scientists means ‘if what scientists say is true’.",
            "answers": [
                "After",
                "According to",
                "In accordance with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy jumped ……………………….. the wall.",
            "description": "Over can mean on or to the other side of something high.",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "above",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I am interested ……………………….. to fly.",
            "description": "The adjective ‘interested’ is usually followed by ‘in + noun/ ing form’.",
            "answers": [
                "to learn",
                "in learning",
                "at learning"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am anxious for my daughter ……………………….. a good job.",
            "description": "Anxious to get means eager to get.",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "to getting",
                "about getting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My ………………………. jobs were very stressful.",
            "description": "The adjectives first, second, next and last usually go before one, two, three etc.",
            "answers": [
                "two last",
                "last two",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "My husband is six years ……………………….. than me.",
            "description": "The adjectives elder and eldest can only be used before a noun. After a verb we use other words like older and oldest. Here we use ‘elder’ because we need a comparative form before ‘than’.",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t remember him ………………………",
            "description": "Well is an adverb good is an adjective. We need an adverb to modify a verb.",
            "answers": [
                "well",
                "good",
                "better"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I could read only the ...................................... chapters of the book.",
            "description": "The adjectives first, second, next and last usually go before one, two, three etc.",
            "answers": [
                "five first",
                "first five"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has few reasons for staying, ..................................?",
            "description": "Clauses with little and few are followed by affirmative question tags. ",
            "answers": [
                "has he",
                "hasn't he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}